A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants Them-Tw FA732H FA732H
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - Them to Tw, 1937-2006
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (06800595), 1968 June 28-1969 June 27 (Reel R2241)
    $10,094.00;$10,094.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (06800788), 1968 August 15-1969 November 14 (Reel R2247)
    RECRUITING, COUNSELING, TUTORING AND CARRYING ON ORIENTATION ACTIVITIES FOR NEGRO FRESHMEN IN THE FALL OF 1968
    $51,200.00;$51,200.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (06900074), 1968 November 19-1969 November 18 (Reel R1592)
    SUPPORT OF A WORLD CONFERENCE ON .THE ROLE OF THE UNIVERSITY IN THE QUEST FOR PEACE.
    Gordon, Stanley
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (06900161), 1969 January 22-1975 May 31 (Reel R1334)
    FELLOWSHIPS FOR M.A. AND PH.D. CANDIDATES IN CRIMINAL JUSTICE
    $251,000.00;$251,000.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (06900461), 1969 May 29-1970 May 28 (Reel R1945)
    $13,722.00;$13,309.76
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (06900485), 1969 June 01-1977 June 30 (Reel R1254)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FO THE DOCTORAL PROGRAM IN THE POLICY SCIENCES AT THE STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK AT BUFFALO
    $250,000.00;$249,969.69
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07000096), 1969 October 01-1982 December 31 (Reel R3559, Reel R4056)
    SUPPORT OF A FAMILY PLANNING DEMONSTRATION CLINIC AND TRAINING PROGRAM FOR NURSE-MIDWIVES FROM DEVELOPING COUNTRIES
    $135,905.00;$135,905.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07000135), 1969 October 01-1971 September 30 (Reel R1655, Reel R4543)
    GRADUATE ENGLISH LANGUAGE PROGRAM AT THE TEACHERS TRAINING COLLEGE (IKIP) IN MALANG, INDONESIA
    $109,200.00;$109,200.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07000314), 1970 June 01-1972 September 30 (Reel R1691)
    STUDIES OF THE STATE-LOCAL SECURITIES MARKET
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07000325), 1970 June 15-1972 June 15 (Reel R1667)
    SUPPORT OF STUDIES ON THE ECONOMICS OF WELFARE
    $42,515.00;$42,514.87
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07000346), 1970 June 09-1973 June 08 (Reel R1070)
    PROGRAM IN APPLIED ENVIRONMENTAL ANALYSIS AND DESIGN
    $368,000.00;$367,997.09
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07000585), 1970 (Reel R1706)
    $4,870.00;$4,660.55
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07000586), 1970 (Reel R1706)
    $3,000.00;$.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07100127), 1971 January 01-1974 December 31 (Reel R2373)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE COSTS OF ASSESSING THE EXPERIMENTAL LEARNING SYSTEM AT EMPIRE STATE COLLEGE
    $510,000.00;$510,000.00
    Spangeberg, Gail
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07100178), 1971 March 01-1973 February 28 (Reel R1723, Reel R1724)
    RESEARCH ON CRIMINAL JUSTICE PLANNING AND PROJECTIONS
    $102,000.00;$100,014.81
    Roditti, Esther C.
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07100250), 1971 September 01-1972 August 31 (Reel R1729)
    $4,602.00;$4,602.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07100358), 1971 June 08-1972 December 07 (Reel R1738)
    $15,683.00;$15,674.13
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07100359), 1971 June 08-1972 December 07 (Reel R1738)
    $19,452.00;$19,164.95
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07100525), 1971 September 15-1972 September 14 (Reel R1838)
    CORE SUPPORT FOR A PROJECT OF TRAINING STATE AND LOCAL GOVERNMENT OFFICIALS IN NEW YORK STATE
    $71,000.00;$70,674.70
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07200026), 1971 July 01-1974 December 31 (Reel R1501)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A GRADUATE PROGRAM IN KODALY-BASED MUSICAL TRAINING
    $118,606.00;$118,606.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07200287), 1972 July 26-1974 January 25 (Reel R1746, Reel R1747)
    $16,568.00;$14,369.36
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07400290), 1974 March 15-1977 January 31 (Reel R1543)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH PROGRAMS IN PRODUCTIVITY IMPROVEMENT IN STATE GOVERNMENT
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07450316), 1974 October 01-1974 October 31 (Reel R1477)
    SEMINAR FOR SUNY INSTITUTIONS ON ASSESSMENT OF EXPERIMENTAL LEARNING AT EMPIRE STATE COLLEGE
    $4,250.00;$3,478.86
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07550473), 1975 August 15-1976 December 31 (Reel R2004, Reel R2005)
    SUPPORT FOR A COMPAROTIVE STUDY OF COLLEGE ORGANIZATION AND STUDENT OUTCOMES
    $25,000.00;$23,416.79
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07650277), 1976 June 01-1978 August 31 (Reel R3740)
    AN ANALYSIS OF PUBLIC AND PRIVATE INSURANCE AS WELL AS OTHER GUARANTEES FOR STATE AND LOCAL GOVERNMENT SECURITIES
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07700632), 1977 October 01-1980 September 30 (Reel R2309, Reel R2310)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT TO DEVELOP A DEGREE PROGRAM FOR NYC PUERTO RICAN AND HISPANIC WORKING ADULTS INVOLVING EMPIRE STATE COLLEGE
    $95,000.00;$94,986.24
    Coolen, Marion A.;Payton, Benjamin Franklin
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07800397), 1978 January 02-1979 September 30 (Reel R2788)
    STUDY OF THE NEW YORK STATE CIVIL SERVICE SYSTEM AS IT EFFECTS WOMEN IN PUBLIC EMPLOYMENT
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07850860), 1978 September 01-1979 May 31 (Reel R2528)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON THE "IMPACT OF INTERNATIONAL ECONOMIC DISTURBANCES ON THE SOVIET UNION AND EASTERN EUROPE"
    $6,000.00;$5,985.19
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (07950063), 1978 December 01-1980 December 31 (Reel R2375)
    CONFERENCE ON PATTERNS OF THE LABOR FORCE IN SOUTHERN AFRICA
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08000521), 1980 May 01-1992 December 31 (Reel R6388, Reel R6389)
    SUPPORT TO IDENTIFY & REMOVE SYSTEMIC BARRIERS TO THE ADVANCEMENT OF WOMEN IN GOVERNMENT EMPLOYMENT
    $1,515,000.00;$1,515,000.00
    Zeitlin, June H.
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08050398), 1980 March 03-1980 December 31 (Reel R2754)
    SUPPORT TO PRINT COPIES OF A RECENT STUDY, "SEX SEGREGATED CAREER LADDERS IN NEW YORK STATE GOVERNMENT EMPLOYMENT: A STRUCTURAL.....
    $2,200.00;$2,185.62
    Vance, Amy S.
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08150338), 1981 February 01-1981 July 31 (Reel R4216)
    TO SUPPORT A STUDY OF THE PROMOTION OF MINORITIES TO HIGH LEVEL POSITIONS IN STATE GOVERNMENT
    $10,200.00;$10,195.83
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08250600), 1982 April 01-1983 March 31 (Reel R3634)
    SUPPORT TO HELP THE CHINESE ACADEMY FOR SOCIAL SCIENCES ACQUIRE ECONOMICS JOURNALS AND PERIODICALS
    $18,490.00;$18,300.15
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08350072), 1982 November 01-1984 April 30 (Reel R4245)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND PRODUCTION OF THE "POLITICAL HANDBOOK OF THE WORLD" AND THE "ECONOMIC HANDBOOK OF THE WORLD"
    $49,919.00;$49,919.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08350077), 1982 October 29-1983 October 28 (Reel R4180)
    TUITION FEES FOR FIVE KENYAN AGRICULTURAL STUDENTS
    $8,750.00;$8,335.96
    Jones, David B.
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08350820), 1983 June 01-1986 December 31 (Reel R5353)
    TRAINING FOR TWO BLACK SOUTHERN AFRICANS THROUGH PARTICIPATION IN POLITICAL AND ECONOMIC RESEARCH
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08350843), 1983 November 01-1991 August 31 (Reel R6206)
    SUPPORT FOR AN EXHIBITION ON THE WORK OF NATIVE AMERICAN ARTISTS
    $20,000.00;$19,970.31
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08400623), 1984 June 01-1988 May 31 (Reel R5984)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON THE MARIEL BOAT-LIFT
    International Affairs Program [IA];Developing Country Programs [DCP];Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ]
    $158,000.00;$150,178.52
    Balaran, Paul;McClymont, Mary (Mary E.)
    Cuba
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08450267), 1984 February 15-1984 November 14 (Reel R4602)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR INDEPENDENT COMMISSION ON MISSION, GOVERNANCE, AND FUTURE OF STATE UNIVERSITY OF NEW YORK
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08550274), 1985 January 01-1988 June 30 (Reel R6048)
    PROVIDE SUPPORT FOR PROJECT TO IMPROVE COLLEGE TEACHING
    Bernstein, Alison R.;Biddle, Sheila
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08551062), 1985 October 01-1989 September 30 (Reel R6194)
    SUPPORT FOR PROJECT IDENTIFYING UNDERGRADUATE AND GRADUATE CURRICULUM RESOURCES IN CHICANO STUDIES
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08600314), 1986 March 01-1988 December 31 (Reel R6225)
    SUPPORT FOR A SYSTEMWIDE EFFORT TO PROMOTE TRANSFER FROM COMMUNITY TO FOUR-YEAR COLLEGES
    $165,000.00;$164,325.71
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08600563), 1985 September 01-1991 December 31 (Reel R6162, Reel R6544, Reel R6707)
    SUPPORT FOR COLLABORATIVE RESEARCH AND TRAINING BETWEEN AN AFRICAN AND AN AMERICAN UNIVERSITY
    Eastern Africa (Nairobi);Developing Country Programs [DCP]
    Chege, Michael;Quarterman, Mark
    Mozambique
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08650299), 1986 April 01-1987 June 30 (Reel R5619)
    STUDY OF NEW YORK CITY-NEW YORK STATE RELATIONS AND IMPLICATIONS FOR OTHER LARGE CITIES AND STATE GOVERNMENTS
    United States; New York (N.Y.); New York (State)
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08700687), 1987 May 01-1992 December 31 (Reel R6612, Reel R6613, Reel R6614)
    NATIONAL RESEARCH PROJECT ENTITLED "CHANGING RELATIONS: NEWCOMERS AND ESTABLISHED RESIDENTS IN U.S. COMMUNITIES"
    $2,102,500.00;$2,102,500.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08750401), 1986 December 01-1987 June 30 (Reel R5292)
    SUPPORT FOR TEAM OF SOCIAL SCIENTISTS TO ASSESS REQUIREMENTS FOR STUDIES ON RELATIONS AMONG NEWCOMERS AND ESTABLISHED U.S.RESIDENTS
    $24,000.00;$23,388.36
    Morris, Diana L.
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08750753), 1987 July 01-1989 January 01 (Reel R5824)
    RESEARCH CONFERENCE ON TARGETING STATE PROGRAMS AND RESOURCES TO DISTRESSED PLACES AND LOW INCOME PEOPLE
    $43,500.00;$43,487.14
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08751059), 1987 September 01-1988 August 31 (Reel R6197)
    EXPLORATORY RESEARCH INTO THE PARTICIPATION IN MATHEMATICS OF HIGH-POTENTIAL, LOW ACHIEVING MINORITY GIRLS
    $49,900.00;$49,900.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08800631), 1988 July 01-1993 September 30 (Reel R6373)
    SUPPORT FOR A RESEARCH PROJECT ON "MIGRATION, DEVELOPMENT AND FOREIGN RELATIONS IN THE CARIBBEAN."
    $228,550.00;$221,367.07
    Isaacs, Anita;O'Cleireacain, Seamus
    Canada; Cuba; United States
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08850494), 1988 April 01-1988 September 30 (Reel R5797)
    SUPPORT TO ALLOW ASIAN HUMAN RIGHTS SCHOLARS TO ATTEND A CONFERENCE ON HUMAN RIGHTS IN SOUTH AND SOUTHEAST ASIA
    $25,000.00;$15,880.38
    Hicks, Frank
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (08900626), 1989 April 01-1995 May 31 (Reel R6955)
    SUPPORT TO DEVELOP A SUMMER INTERNSHIP PROGRAM AT INTERNATIONAL ORGANIZATIONS IN GENEVA FOR GRAD. STUDENTS FROM U.S. UNIVERSITIES
    $276,240.00;$276,240.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09000768), 1990 April 01-1992 June 30 (Reel R6279, Reel R6280)
    SUPPORT FOR PROJECTS THAT MAINSTREAM RESEARCH ON MINORITY WOMEN INTO UNDERGRADUATE LIBERAL ARTS CURRICULA
    Northeastern States
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09001508), 1990 October 01-1994 June 01 (Reel R6794)
    RESEARCH & DISSEMINATION PROJECT ON REFUGEE DETERMINATION & ASYLUM ADJUDICATION STANDARDS AND POLICY
    $200,000.00;$159,585.52
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09100673), 1991 July 01-1997 January 31 (Reel R7931)
    Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ];Governance And Public Policy Program [GPP]
    Arnold, David D.;Lipsky, Michael
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09101377), 1991 October 01-1993 September 30 (Reel R6493)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON AND DISSEMINATION OF TECHNIQUES TO DELIVER COMPREHENSIVE SERVICES TO POOR FAMILIES
    $57,500.00;$57,475.13
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09200789), 1992 June 01-1994 May 31 (Reel R6783)
    SUPPORT FOR A STUDY ON THE LEGAL NEEDS AND STATUSES OF LOW-INCOME ALIENS IN THE U.S.
    $500,000.00;$489,834.47
    Diaz, William A.;McClymont, Mary (Mary E.)
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09300295), 1992 November 01-1998 October 31 (Reel R7943)
    SUPPORT FOR THE CENTER FOR THE STUDY OF THE STATES TO ANALYZE TRENDS IN STATE BUDGETS AND TAXES
    $1,100,000.00;$1,100,000.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09350726), 1993 April 01-1994 December 31 (Reel R6832)
    SUPPORT FOR SYMPOSIUM IN RECOGNITION OF 25TH ANNIVERSARY OF THE "REPORT OF THE COMMISSION ON CIVIL DISORDERS" ("KERNER COMMISSION")
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09351542), 1993 December 01-1995 July 31 (Reel R7295)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE ON "RETHINKING WOMEN'S PLACE IN THE GLOBAL ECONOMY"
    Petrovich, Janice;Zwerling, L. Steven
    United States; Women's studies--United States
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09451034), 1994 August 01-1997 January 31 (Reel R7507)
    TO PROVIDE SUPPORT FOR AN ORAL HISTORY PROJECT ENTITLED "GENDER AND DEINDUSTRIALIZATION"
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09500791), 1995 June 01-1998 July 31 (Reel R7948)
    SUPPORT FOR PROJECTS THAT INTEGRATE INTERNATIONAL SCHOLARSHIP INTO U.S. WOMEN'S STUDIES PROGRAMS AND GENDER RESEARCH INTO AREA OR INTERNATIONAL STUDIES PROGRAMS
    $105,600.00;$105,595.60
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09500910), 1995 September 01-1997 August 31 (Reel R7473)
    TO CENTER FOR WOMEN IN GOVERNMENT FOR COLLECTION, ANALYSIS, & DISSEMINATION OF DATA ON WOMEN APPOINTED OFFICIALS IN STATE GOVERNMENT
    $157,000.00;$156,959.44
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09600577), 1996 March 01-1998 June 30 (Reel R8138)
    SUPPORT FOR AN ASSESSMENT OF THE ROLES OF COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CORPORATIONS
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09701359), 1997 September 01-2004 December 31 (Reel R9196)
    SUPPORT FOR WOMEN'S LEADERSHIP DEVELOPMENT AND TO INCREASE UNDERSTANDING OF WOMEN'S CONTRIBUTION TO CIVIC AND POLITICAL LIFE
    $644,000.00;$644,000.00
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09800794), 1998 March 01-2002 December 31 (Reel R9028)
    SUPPORT FOR CONSULTATIONS ON ETHNICITY AND RESEARCH ON POLITICAL ARRANGEMENTS
    $394,000.00;$394,000.00
    Ihonvbere, Julius Omozuanvbo
    Africa; Government -- Citizen participation -- Africa Civil society -- Africa
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09801072), 1998 May 01-2001 June 30 (Reel R8914)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH AND DISSEMINATION OF FINDINGS ON STABLE MINORITY URBAN NEIGHBORHOODS IN THE UNITED STATES
    United States; African American neighborhoods -- United States; Community development -- United States
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09801682), 1998 August 01-2002 July 31 (Reel R9007)
    TO HELP INSTITUTIONALIZE A MASTERS DEGREE PROGRAM IN WOMEN'S STUDIES
    United States; Global; Women's studies--Study and teaching--United States
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09851580), 1998 September 01-2000 June 30 (Reel R8746)
    SUPPORT FOR THE ROCKEFELLER INSTITUTE OF GOVERNMENT TO ENHANCE FACULTY CAPACITY IN BUDGET ANALYSIS
    United States; Fiscal policy -- United States
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09900550), 1998 November 01-2000 October 31 (Reel R8660)
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09950583), 1999 June 01-2000 May 31 (Reel R8465)
    SUPPORT FOR A RESEARCH PROJECT EXAMINING THE ROLE OF JAPANESE-AMERICAN WOMEN IN THE U.S. ARMED FORCES DURING WORLD WAR 11
    Human Rights;Assets - Office of the Vice President
    $60,000.00;$59,983.92
    Coward, E. Walter;Wing, Christine B.
    United States; Intergroup relations -- United States; World War, 1939-1945--Participation--Japanese American women
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09950910), 1999 May 01-2000 March 31 (Reel R8800)
    SUPPORT FOR PLANNING A RESEARCH PROJECT ON "ACCOMMODATING DIFFERENCE: THE POLITICS OF CULTURAL PLULRALISM IN EUROPE"
    $15,300.00;$15,300.00
    Europe; Multiculturalism; Religions--Relations--Research; Religious tolerance--History--Research; Religion--Cross-cultural studies
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (09951221), 1999 May 01-2001 March 31 (Reel R8563)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT TO STUDY THE EARLY IMPACTS OF WELFARE REFORM ON COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT CORPORATIONS
    United States; Community development corporations -- Research -- United States; Housing policy -- United States; Welfare economics--United States
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (10000289), 2000 January 01-2002 December 31 (Reel R9025)
    SUPPLEMENTARY SUPPORT FOR AN INTERDISCIPLINARY RESEARCH PROJECT ON "ACCOMMODATING DIFFERENCE: THE POLITICS OF CULTURAL PLURALISM IN EUROPE"
    $208,000.00;$208,000.00
    Europe; Religions--Relations--Research; Religious tolerance--History--Research
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (10000501), 2000 June 01-2001 May 31 (Reel R8506)
    SUPPORT FOR A DIALOGUE BETWEEN MILITARY OFFICERS FROM LATIN AMERICA, THE U.S., AND NIGERIA, AND NIGERIAN PARLIAMENTARIANS ON DEMOCRATIC CONSOLIDATION AND CIVIL-MILITARY RELATIONS
    West Africa (Lagos);Governance and Civil Society
    $173,000.00;$173,000.00
    Nigeria; Democracy -- Nigeria
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (10100789), 2001 April 01-2002 March 31 (Reel R9185)
    Planning grant for the establishment of a regional parliamentary project (The East African Parliamentary Institute)
    $180,000.00;$168,857.84
    Africa, East; Democracy -- Africa, Eastern; Constitutional law -- Africa, Eastern
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (10101598), 2001 August 01-2004 July 31 (Reel R9170)
    For a public education and media outreach project using Census 2000 data to analyze residential patterns of racial and ethnic groups, with a focus on residential segregation in metropolitan areas
    United States; Discrimination in Housing -- United States; Census -- United States
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (10251056), 2002 April 01-2003 August 31 (Reel R9086)
    For research on recent, mostly undocumented immigrants to the U.S. from China's Fujian province, their histories and their impact on the sending and host communities
    Higashi, Taryn;Campbell, Elizabeth C.
  - The Research Foundation of State University of New York (10450146), 2003 November 01-2004 October 31 (Reel R9138)
    For the Purchase College School of Humanities to conduct research and public education on the religious and cultural pluralism of "Christian Europe"
    $64,000.00;$64,000.00
  - The Retail Initiative, Inc. (10101167), 2001 June 01-2002 May 31 (Reel R9012)
    To develop and implement a strategy to effectively structure, market and utilize the New Markets Tax Credit program
    DeGiovanni, Frank F.;Kahane, Michele F.
    United States; Community development; Economic development
  - The Rhodes National Gallery (06100369), 1961 September 29-1962 September 28 (Reel R0775)
    INTERNATIONAL CONGRESS OF AFRICA CULTURE TO BE HELD IN SALISBURY SOUTHERN RHODESIA
    $50,000.00;$36,909.70
  - The Richmond Symphony, Inc. (06600315), 1966 July 01-1976 June 30 (Reel R2935, Reel R2992, Reel R4342)
    THE RICHMOND SYMPHONY (GENERAL SUPPORT)
  - The Riverside (Ill.) Church in the City of New York (08450156), 1984 January 01-1984 December 31 (Reel R4504)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR ESL INSTRUCTION FOR REFUGEES AND MIGRANTS IN NEW YORK CITY
    $49,500.00;$48,638.30
    Biggers, Patricia
  - The Robert A. Taft Institute of Government (09251192), 1992 October 01-1993 September 30 (Reel R6677)
    FOR MINORITY YOUTH-FOCUSED CIVIC PARTICIPATION ACTIVITIES.
  - The Robert R. Moton Memorial Institute, Inc. (06600067), 1965 December 14-1970 December 13 (Reel R1439)
    CONFERENCES AND IMPROVEMENT OF THE FOUNDATION'S CONFERENCE CENTER AT CAPAHOSIC, VIRGINIA
  - The Robert R. Moton Memorial Institute, Inc. (06800732), 1968 July 17-1970 July 16 (Reel R2244)
    ESTABLISHMENT OF MODEL COLLEGE DEVELOPMENT OFFICE AND REFERENCE LIBRARY ON FUNDRAISING
    $69,000.00;$69,000.00
    Bryant, James W.
  - The Robert R. Moton Memorial Institute, Inc. (07300140), 1973 January 01-1973 December 31 (Reel R1766)
    TWO WORKSHOPS ON FOUNDATION RELATIONS & FOUNDATION RESEARCH & PROVISION OF BASIC FOUNDATION RESEARCH SERVICE FOR 86 BLACK INSTIT
    $105,140.00;$104,640.00
    Jordan, James R.;Payton, Benjamin Franklin
  - The Robert R. Moton Memorial Institute, Inc. (07700040), 1976 July 01-1978 June 30 (Reel R2379)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF AN ACADEMIC AND INTERN FELLOWSHIP PROGRAM TO IDENTIFY AND DEVELOP LEADERSHIP ON THE MODEL AND IN THE NAME OF...
    $122,298.67;$122,298.67
  - The Robey Theatre Company (10551332), 2005 October 01-2006 November 30 (Reel R9081)
    For developmental expenses for the Playwrights Lab and Reading Series
  - The Rockefeller University (07400255), 1974 July 01-1979 December 31 (Reel R2286, Reel R3855)
    CROSS CULTURAL STUDIES IN LITERACY AND COGNITION
    Education and Public Policy;International - Office of the Vice President [ID/OVP]
    $234,705.00;$234,705.00
    Barber, Elinor G.;Lynch, Barbara D.;Martus, Marjorie
  - The Rockefeller University (07500021), 1974 September 15-1978 September 30 (Reel R2306)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF A SERIES OF PROCESS ORIENTED STUDIES OF COGNITIVE DEVELOPMENT DURING ADOLESCENCE
    $143,632.00;$143,632.00
  - The Rockefeller University (07500284), 1975 July 01-1979 August 15 (Reel R2497, Reel R2741)
    SUPPORT FOR A MULTI ETHNIC, MULTI DISCIPLINARY TRAINING PROGRAM INRESEARCH ON THE RELATION BETWEEN CULTURE AND MENTAL PROCESSES
    $300,000.00;$299,950.60
    Lynch, Barbara D.;Martus, Marjorie
  - The Rockefeller University (07800369), 1978 May 18-1981 May 17 (Reel R4145)
    SUPPORT OF ACTIVITIES OF THE COUNCIL ON SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY FOR DEVELOPMENT
    $250,000.00;$25,000.00
    Carmichael, William D.(William Daniel)
  - The Rockefeller University (07850056), 1977 October 01-1978 March 31 (Reel R3544)
    SUPPORT FOR INITIAL ACTIVITIES OF THE COUNCIL ON SCIENCE AND TECHNOLOGY FOR DEVELOPMENT
  - The Rockefeller University (07850310), 1978 March 15-1979 June 30 (Reel R2922)
    STUDY OF CHILDREN'S WRITING AND PREPARATION OF A PAPER FOR TEACHERDEALING WITH PROBLEMS CHILDREN ENCOUNTER IN LEARNING TO WRITE
    $18,150.00;$18,150.00
  - The Rockefeller University (09450718), 1994 April 01-1995 March 31 (Reel R6749)
    SUPPORT FOR CONFERENCE ON PHILANTHROPY IN ASIA
    Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ];Asia & The Pacific [ASIA]
    Geithner, Peter F.;Seltzer, Michael